<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HackForGood</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    
    <string name="education"><b>Compulsory education</b>\n\nIn Spain, all foreigners under the age of 16 have the full right to access the compulsory education of the educational system. In such a way that they can access scholarships and grants and obtain the corresponding academic degree under the same conditions as Spaniards.\n
The right to basic education is guaranteed regardless of the legal status of the family. Whether the parents are in an irregular situation, as if they are refugees or meet the requirements to be residents, the sons or daughters must also attend school.
<a href="https://web.gencat.cat/es/temes/educacio/index.html">https://web.gencat.cat/es/temes/educacio/index.html</a>\n
If you are over 18 years old and wish to obtain the title of Graduate in Compulsory Secondary Education, you can take the test to directly obtain the title <a href="https://educacio.gencat.cat/ca/serveis-tramits/proves/ proves-lliures-obtencio-titols/obtencio-geso-mes-18-anys/">https://educacio.gencat.cat/ca/serveis-tramits/proves/proves-lliures-obtencio-titols/obtencio-geso- month-18-anys/</a>

\n<b>Post-compulsory education</b>\n
All foreign minors and resident foreigners over 18 years of age have the right to access post-compulsory educational stages, obtain the corresponding qualifications and scholarships and grants under the same conditions as Spaniards.\n
Therefore, if you are a migrant or refugee and wish to continue your post-compulsory education outside your country of origin, you can access any level of the Spanish education system, provided you meet the academic access requirements.
Depending on your previous training and your academic goals, in post-compulsory education there are different training options from which you can choose
<a href="https://web.gencat.cat/es/temes/educacio/index.html">https://web.gencat.cat/es/temes/educacio/index.html</a>\n

\n<b>Learn the language</b>\n
It is usually preferable to learn through courses in order to advance faster, some of them are specialized for migrants and refugees and are free. If you want to complement your course with additional content or be self-taught, this material could be useful.
<a href="https://web.gencat.cat/es/ukraina/persones-refugiades/acollida-cultural-i-linguistica/">https://web.gencat.cat/es/ukraina/persones-refugiades/acollida-cultural-i-linguistica/</a>
\nspanish for kids
<a href="https://carei.es/fich/aprendojugando2.pdf">https://carei.es/fich/aprendojugando2.pdf</a>
<a href="https://www.juntadeandalucia.es/export/drupaljda/13371609561450770.pdf">https://www.juntadeandalucia.es/export/drupaljda/13371609561450770.pdf</a>
<a href="https://espanolparainmigrantes.wordpress.com/">https://espanolparainmigrantes.wordpress.com/</a>
\nRemember that the library service is totally free. A library card allows you to use those public library services that require identification: loan of documents, reservation of Internet computers and multimedia classrooms, registration for courses and workshops, use of Wi-Fi. In addition, it allows you to enjoy many advantages and discounts.<a href="https://bibliotecavirtual.diba.cat/es/ajuda/carnet#:~:text=%C2%BFQu%C3%A9%20se%20necesita%3F,residencia%20indicando%20la%20address%C3%B3n%20postal">https://bibliotecavirtual.diba.cat/es/ajuda/carnet#:~:text=%C2%BFQu%C3%A9%20se%20necesita%3F,residencia%20indicando%20la%20address%C3%B3n%20postal.</a>

    </string>
</resources>