<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HackForGood</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="wanttohelp"><b>How I can help?</b>\n\n 우리 정환은 한극 사람입니다, 제 진구입니다. 제 이르믄 알바입니다, 간가지를 아주 좌입니다 :) 솔고지를 하고 십지 아나여, 시러여.
Making us known on social networks, making a donation or offering your services as a professional. \n<a href="">Click here to know more</a></string>
    <string name="healthcare"><i>Foreign persons who are not registered or authorized as residents in Spain have the right to health protection and health care under the same conditions as persons with Spanish nationality, as established in article 3.1.</i>\n
<a href="https://www.boe.es/boe/dias/2018/07/30/pdfs/BOE-A-2018-10752.pdf">https://www.boe.es/boe/dias/2018/07/30/pdfs/BOE-A-2018-10752.pdf</a>\n
How to get a health \n<a href="https://web.gencat.cat/es/tramits/tramits-temes/8144_-_Targeta_sanitaria_individual_TSI">https://web.gencat.cat/es/tramits/tramits-temes/8144_-_Targeta_sanitaria_individual_TSI</a>\n
\n<b>Psychological help</b>\n\n
Barcelona crisis unit: Psychological assistance telephone free call 900101580 <a href="http://utccb.net/asistencia-psicologica/index.htm">http://utccb.net/asistencia-psicologica/index.htm</a>
Free psychological support service for adults: Konsulta’m +22 <a href="https://ajuntament.barcelona.cat/sanitatisalut/es/noticia/konsultam-amplia-el-apoyo-psicologico-a-la-poblacion-adulta_1134147">https://ajuntament.barcelona.cat/sanitatisalut/es/noticia/konsultam-amplia-el-apoyo-psicologico-a-la-poblacion-adulta_1134147</a>
    </string>
    <string name="education"><b>Compulsory education</b>\n\nIn Spain, all foreigners under the age of 16 have the full right to access the compulsory education of the educational system. In such a way that they can access scholarships and grants and obtain the corresponding academic degree under the same conditions as Spaniards.\n
The right to basic education is guaranteed regardless of the legal status of the family. Whether the parents are in an irregular situation, as if they are refugees or meet the requirements to be residents, the sons or daughters must also attend school.
<a href="https://web.gencat.cat/es/temes/educacio/index.html">https://web.gencat.cat/es/temes/educacio/index.html</a>\n
If you are over 18 years old and wish to obtain the title of Graduate in Compulsory Secondary Education, you can take the test to directly obtain the title <a href="https://educacio.gencat.cat/ca/serveis-tramits/proves/ proves-lliures-obtencio-titols/obtencio-geso-mes-18-anys/">https://educacio.gencat.cat/ca/serveis-tramits/proves/proves-lliures-obtencio-titols/obtencio-geso- month-18-anys/</a>

\n<b>Post-compulsory education</b>\n\n
All foreign minors and resident foreigners over 18 years of age have the right to access post-compulsory educational stages, obtain the corresponding qualifications and scholarships and grants under the same conditions as Spaniards.\n
Therefore, if you are a migrant or refugee and wish to continue your post-compulsory education outside your country of origin, you can access any level of the Spanish education system, provided you meet the academic access requirements.
Depending on your previous training and your academic goals, in post-compulsory education there are different training options from which you can choose
<a href="https://web.gencat.cat/es/temes/educacio/index.html">https://web.gencat.cat/es/temes/educacio/index.html</a>\n

\n<b>Learn the language</b>\n\n
It is usually preferable to learn through courses in order to advance faster, some of them are specialized for migrants and refugees and are free. If you want to complement your course with additional content or be self-taught, this material could be useful.
<a href="https://web.gencat.cat/es/ukraina/persones-refugiades/acollida-cultural-i-linguistica/">https://web.gencat.cat/es/ukraina/persones-refugiades/acollida-cultural-i-linguistica/</a>
\nspanish for kids
<a href="https://carei.es/fich/aprendojugando2.pdf">https://carei.es/fich/aprendojugando2.pdf</a>
<a href="https://www.juntadeandalucia.es/export/drupaljda/13371609561450770.pdf">https://www.juntadeandalucia.es/export/drupaljda/13371609561450770.pdf</a>
<a href="https://espanolparainmigrantes.wordpress.com/">https://espanolparainmigrantes.wordpress.com/</a>
\nRemember that the library service is totally free. A library card allows you to use those public library services that require identification: loan of documents, reservation of Internet computers and multimedia classrooms, registration for courses and workshops, use of Wi-Fi. In addition, it allows you to enjoy many advantages and discounts.<a href="https://bibliotecavirtual.diba.cat/es/ajuda/carnet#:~:text=%C2%BFQu%C3%A9%20se%20necesita%3F,residencia%20indicando%20la%20address%C3%B3n%20postal">https://bibliotecavirtual.diba.cat/es/ajuda/carnet#:~:text=%C2%BFQu%C3%A9%20se%20necesita%3F,residencia%20indicando%20la%20address%C3%B3n%20postal.</a>
    </string>

    <string name="foodaid"><b>Where can I get food?</b>\n\n
The main source of supply is the Food Bank (<a href="https://www.bancdelsaliments.org/es/ayuda-alimentaria">https://www.bancdelsaliments.org/es/ayuda-alimentaria</a>), but there are also religious organizations and associations that fulfill the same function. You may also be interested in obtaining a Money Card that facilitates Social Services, the management of financial aid for food, as well as the access of families to fresh food and other basic products <a href="https://www.diba.cat /en/web/benestar/card-wallet
">https://www.diba.cat/es/web/benestar/targeta-moneder</a>\n
<b>These are the nearest food aid centers:</b>
<a href="http://www.l-h.cat/serveisocials/262731_1.aspx?id=1"
>http://www.l-h.cat/serveisocials/262731_1.aspx?id=1</a>
Mare de Déu de Bellvitge Parish: <a href="https://www.fundaciolavinya.org/es/que-fem/projecte/banc-daliments
">https://www.fundaciolavinya.org/es/que-fem/projecte/banc-daliments</a>
<a href="https://caritas.barcelona/en/need-help/">https://caritas.barcelona/en/needed-help/</a>\n

<b>Where can I eat?</b>\n\n
You do not always have access to a kitchen or despite having one, it can happen that the cost of electricity and gas makes cooking unfeasible. That doesn\'t mean you have to go hungry.
<b>These are the closest soup kitchens:</b>\n
Dining room for the elderly: <a href="https://www.papelea.com/ayuntamiento-de-hospitalet-de-llobregat/eater-para-personas-mayores"> https://www.papelea.com/ayuntamiento -de-hospitalet-de-llobregat/canteen-for-elderly-people</a>
Restaurant and Social Menjador "La Terrasseta" Carrer de la Fraternitat, 40, 08012 Barcelona 934 15 62 98\n
<b>Where can my children eat?</b>\n\n
Children can access the soup kitchens accompanied by their parents. Also, if they are in school they can eat in the school canteen. With a canteen scholarship you can reduce your cost and be able to be fully covered.
\n<b>Application for a canteen scholarship:</b><a href="https://www.edubcn.cat/es/alumnado_y_familia/ayudas_becas_y_subvenciones/ayudas_de_dining_school"> https://www.edubcn.cat/es/alumnado_y_familia /aid_scholarships_and_subsidies/aid_for_school_dining_room</a>
    </string>
</resources>